<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jobAlerts>
   <jobAlert>
      <position>Full Stack Java JEE Developer</position>
      <detail>VIC-Melbourne, Exciting growth at this org Work with recognisable clients &amp; new tech Industry training &amp; certifications Opportunity to work in a full stack capacity with the latest tech for some very recognisable clients Your new company This company prides itself on excellence utilising new technologies for cutting edge applications for some very recognisable clients. As they continue to grow, an opportunity ha</detail>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Full-Stack-Java-JEE-Developer-Job-Melbourne-VIC-AU-166242411.aspx</link>
      <guid>166242411</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:17:16 GMT</pubDate>
   </jobAlert>
   <jobAlert>
      <position>Java Analyst Programmer / Full Stack Developer</position>
      <detail>QLD-Brisbane, Permanent role Great organisation culture Looking for a mid level Full Stack Developer with experience in Java, JavaScript and Angular JS for a permanent role as an Analyst Programmer in Brisbane. The company: The company is a large organisation specialising in the ICT industry with a collaborative yet autonomous culture. A market leader and a well known provider of their service with focus on pro</detail>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Java-Analyst-Programmer-Full-Stack-Developer-Job-Brisbane-QLD-AU-166203484.aspx</link>
      <guid>166203484</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:27:31 GMT</pubDate>
   </jobAlert>
   <jobAlert>
      <position>Java Developer</position>
      <detail>QLD-Brisbane, 3 Month Fixed Term Contract initially, get extended for up to 12 months Large government organisation - CBD Location Get in touch to find out more A large government organisation has a large budget to employ a Java Developer in Brisbane. This will be an initial 3 month Fixed Term contract, at the successful completion of probation, candidates will be extended up to 12 months. You must be an Austra</detail>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Java-Developer-Job-Brisbane-QLD-AU-166203707.aspx</link>
      <guid>166203707</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:28:26 GMT</pubDate>
   </jobAlert>
   <jobAlert>
      <position>Senior Java Developer</position>
      <detail>VIC-Melbourne, Work with very recognisable clients Opportunity to work with the latest tech Industry training &amp; certifications Leading Australian organisation is seeking passionate Developers to join an exciting phase at the company Your new company This company prides itself on excellence utilising new technologies for cutting edge applications for some very recognisable clients. As they continue to grow, an op</detail>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Senior-Java-Developer-Job-Melbourne-VIC-AU-166867321.aspx</link>
      <guid>166867321</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:32:08 GMT</pubDate>
   </jobAlert>
   <jobAlert>
      <position>Java Analyst Programmer / Full Stack Developer</position>
      <detail>QLD-Brisbane, Permanent role Great organisation culture Looking for a mid level Full Stack Developer with experience in Java, JavaScript and Angular JS for a permanent role as an Analyst Programmer in Brisbane. The company: The company is a large organisation specialising in the ICT industry with a collaborative yet autonomous culture. A market leader and a well known provider of their service with focus on pro</detail>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Java-Analyst-Programmer-Full-Stack-Developer-Job-Brisbane-QLD-AU-166515398.aspx</link>
      <guid>166515398</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:31:58 GMT</pubDate>
   </jobAlert>
   <jobAlert>
      <position>Java/J2EE Developer</position>
      <detail>NSW-Sydney, Leading Media Company Sydney Based Office Crucial Development Project Java Developer/J2EE Developer x2 Hudson Global Resources are currently working with a leading media company that are looking to bring in 2x Java/J2EE Developers into their team on an initial 12 month fixed term contract with a strong chance of extension and/or permanent employment. In this role you will be working on a high prof</detail>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Java-J2EE-Developer-Job-Sydney-NSW-AU-167186341.aspx</link>
      <guid>167186341</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:34:27 GMT</pubDate>
   </jobAlert>
   <jobAlert>
      <position>Java Analyst/Programmer</position>
      <detail>QLD-Brisbane, ASX Listed fast growing business Exposure to the latest technologies Inner north suburbs Attractive package Client Details Our client is a forward-thinking, leading technology solution provider. An ASX listed business, this organization looks at the bigger picture, and is now set to spearhead the company's drive into contemporary technologies and cloud based computing. Description As a Senior memb</detail>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Java-Analyst-Programmer-Job-Brisbane-QLD-AU-166940436.aspx</link>
      <guid>166940436</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:33:24 GMT</pubDate>
   </jobAlert>
   <jobAlert>
      <position>Java Web Developer</position>
      <detail>VIC-Melbourne, ASAP Start. 3 months + extension. Exciting project. Your new company Your new organisation will allow you to join a well respected group within the Victorian Public Sector. Your new role Your new role will be based on a 3 month contract + possible extension and you will be working closely with the development team with the opportunity for possible extension. As a Java Web Developer this is a great</detail>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Java-Web-Developer-Job-Melbourne-VIC-AU-166507153.aspx</link>
      <guid>166507153</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:31:56 GMT</pubDate>
   </jobAlert>
   <jobAlert>
      <position>Java Developer</position>
      <detail>QLD-Brisbane, 3 Month Fixed Term Contract initially, get extended for up to 12 months Large government organisation - CBD Location Get in touch to find out more A large government organisation has a large budget to employ a Java Developer in Brisbane. This will be an initial 3 month Fixed Term contract, at the successful completion of probation, candidates will be extended up to 12 months. You must be an Austra</detail>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Java-Developer-Job-Brisbane-QLD-AU-166515119.aspx</link>
      <guid>166515119</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:31:58 GMT</pubDate>
   </jobAlert>
   <jobAlert>
      <position>Senior Java Developer</position>
      <detail>NSW-Alexandria, Contract Extentions Cutting edge Technologies My Client are Looking for A Senior Java Developer for an initial 3 month contract based in Sydney. This role will see you working with leading edge technologies to build products and services to change the way my client currently uses their digital technology. Does this sound like something that would interest you? We are looking for someone who wants </detail>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Senior-Java-Developer-Job-Alexandria-NSW-AU-167232067.aspx</link>
      <guid>167232067</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:41:09 GMT</pubDate>
   </jobAlert>
   <jobAlert>
      <position>Senior Java Developer</position>
      <detail>QLD-Brisbane, Industry leader in financial services Exposure to the latest technologies Attractive package Genuine career growth and great internal training and development Client Details Our client is a forward-thinking industry leader in the financial services space. An ASX listed business and recognised Employer of Choice, the business is enjoying ongoing growth and is now seen as one of Queensland's best IT</detail>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Senior-Java-Developer-Job-Brisbane-QLD-AU-167428450.aspx</link>
      <guid>167428450</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 18:31:24 GMT</pubDate>
   </jobAlert>
   <jobAlert>
      <position>Java JEE Developer</position>
      <detail>VIC-Melbourne, CBD location, Leader in the software industry Exciting projects, supportive environment Competitive salary + benefits Join an exciting phase of growth at a cutting edge software organisation based in Melbourne's CBD Your new company This organisation is a Melbourne-based company providing quality software design and development services to assist with vital problem solving. As they continue to gro</detail>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Java-JEE-Developer-Job-Melbourne-VIC-AU-166859742.aspx</link>
      <guid>166859742</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 00:05:08 GMT</pubDate>
   </jobAlert>
   <jobAlert>
      <position>Senior Java Developer</position>
      <detail>VIC-Melbourne, Undertaking significant growth Work with recognisable clients &amp; new tech Industry training &amp; certifications Senior Developer role located in Melbourne CBD. Join an exciting phase working with the latest technology. Your new company This company prides itself on excellence utilising new technologies for cutting edge applications for some very recognisable clients. As they continue to grow, an oppor</detail>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Senior-Java-Developer-Job-Melbourne-VIC-AU-166195801.aspx</link>
      <guid>166195801</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 00:07:12 GMT</pubDate>
   </jobAlert>
   <jobAlert>
      <position>Algorithm Performance Lead Engineer</position>
      <detail>ACT-Canberra, Award-winning company Great team and highly technical environment Contact Ivan on 62579802 for further information Join an award-winning company in a permanent job using data to validate algorithmic performance in C+/C#/Java Your new company Join a multi-award winning technology company based in Canberra which specialises in computer vision and high fidelity algorithms which are deployed in real-w</detail>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Algorithm-Performance-Lead-Engineer-Job-Canberra-ACT-AU-167174492.aspx</link>
      <guid>167174492</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 00:08:25 GMT</pubDate>
   </jobAlert>
   <jobAlert>
      <position>Senior Ruby Developer - 6 month Contract</position>
      <detail>NSW-North Sydney, Competitive Salary package 6 month Contract Excellent Culture About the role: This established, global organisation is searching for an experience Ruby Developer to join their growing and talented team of developers responsible for a realm of public facing, high trafficked web applications within the Digital Technology team. You'll be responsible for: This role is highly technical; you will be res</detail>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Senior-Ruby-Developer-6-month-Contract-Job-North-Sydney-NSW-AU-167436911.aspx</link>
      <guid>167436911</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 03:00:16 GMT</pubDate>
   </jobAlert>
   <jobAlert>
      <position>Backend Systems Engineer</position>
      <detail>NSW-Sydney, ManageFlitter – http://manageflitter.com – is a multi-award winning SaaS social media management product. ManageFlitter is used by over 3 million people around the world with paid customers from over 100 countries. We believe social media is changing the world and we love being part of that change. ManageFlitter is profitable and growing fast. ManageFlitter is headquartered in Sydney and with cust</detail>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Backend-Systems-Engineer-Job-Sydney-NSW-AU-167436538.aspx</link>
      <guid>167436538</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 02:30:24 GMT</pubDate>
   </jobAlert>
   <jobAlert>
      <position>Salesforce Developer (6 Month Contract)</position>
      <detail>NSW-Woolloomooloo, 6 month contract Salesforce Development Telco The Client which is a big brand, employee centric, technically leading edge Telco Company, requires a Salesforce Developer / Software Engineer. Main technical skills - APEX, VisualForce, IDE, Salesforce.com API and SQL. The role is very much a specialist 'code', rather than 'click' salesforce role. The role requires someone from a development backgroun</detail>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Salesforce-Developer-6-Month-Contract-Job-Woolloomooloo-NSW-AU-166937730.aspx</link>
      <guid>166937730</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:24:53 GMT</pubDate>
   </jobAlert>
   <jobAlert>
      <position>Salesforce Developer (6 Month Contract)</position>
      <detail>NSW-Abbotsbury, 6 month contract Salesforce Development Telco The Client which is a big brand, employee centric, technically leading edge Telco Company, requires a Salesforce Developer / Software Engineer. Main technical skills - APEX, VisualForce, IDE, Salesforce.com API and SQL. The role is very much a specialist 'code', rather than 'click' salesforce role. The role requires someone from a development backgroun</detail>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Salesforce-Developer-6-Month-Contract-Job-Abbotsbury-NSW-AU-166937743.aspx</link>
      <guid>166937743</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:24:53 GMT</pubDate>
   </jobAlert>
   <jobAlert>
      <position>Salesforce Tech Lead (Contract $800pd)</position>
      <detail>NSW-Woolloomooloo, Salesforce Apex/visual force Contract This Client which is a global brand, employee centric, technically leading edge organisation, requires a Salesforce Developer / Software Engineer. Main technical skills - APEX, VisualForce, IDE, Salesforce.com API and SQL. The role is very much a specialist 'code', rather than 'click' salesforce role. The role requires someone from a development background, ra</detail>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Salesforce-Tech-Lead-Contract-800pd-Job-Woolloomooloo-NSW-AU-166937742.aspx</link>
      <guid>166937742</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:24:53 GMT</pubDate>
   </jobAlert>
   <jobAlert>
      <position>Salesforce Tech Lead (Contract $800pd)</position>
      <detail>NSW-Woolloomooloo, Salesforce Apex/visual force Contract This Client which is a global brand, employee centric, technically leading edge organisation, requires a Salesforce Developer / Software Engineer. Main technical skills - APEX, VisualForce, IDE, Salesforce.com API and SQL. The role is very much a specialist 'code', rather than 'click' salesforce role. The role requires someone from a development background, ra</detail>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Salesforce-Tech-Lead-Contract-800pd-Job-Woolloomooloo-NSW-AU-166937729.aspx</link>
      <guid>166937729</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:24:53 GMT</pubDate>
   </jobAlert>
   <jobAlert>
      <position>Front End Web Developer - Temporary &amp; Permanent opportunities</position>
      <detail>QLD-Brisbane, Industry leader Enterprise level, Agile development environment Attractive salary/hourly rate Convenient location Client Details An industry leader in the insurance space, based conveniently in Brisbane’s inner suburbs, is currently expanding their online presence exponentially and taking on new exciting products. Driving the latest technologies and with the opportunity to work at the cutting edge</detail>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Front-End-Web-Developer-Temporary-Permanent-opportunities-Job-Brisbane-QLD-AU-166529329.aspx</link>
      <guid>166529329</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:31:23 GMT</pubDate>
   </jobAlert>
   <jobAlert>
      <position>Mobile Aplication Developer</position>
      <detail>WA-Perth, Contract position Long term potential Immediate start Our Perth based client currently has a unique opportunity available for a proven Mobile Application Developer. This exciting opportunity would suit an Mobile Developer with ideally 2-3 years commercial experience and offers the opportunity join a growing team and take part in some exciting greenfields product development. This will initially be</detail>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Mobile-Aplication-Developer-Job-Perth-WA-AU-166872632.aspx</link>
      <guid>166872632</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:32:21 GMT</pubDate>
   </jobAlert>
   <jobAlert>
      <position>eCommerce Web Master</position>
      <detail>VIC-Melbourne, Global leading brands, Surf Coast location, Dynamic and professional team environment Responsibilities: Day-to-day management, maintenance, monitoring and configuration of existing eCommerce websites eCommerce platform functional testing, debugging and release management Website infrastructure and hosting management Assist in new eCommerce sites projects Responsible for CRM tools and support Provi</detail>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/eCommerce-Web-Master-Job-Melbourne-VIC-AU-167215373.aspx</link>
      <guid>167215373</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:40:26 GMT</pubDate>
   </jobAlert>
   <jobAlert>
      <position>Senior Front End Developer</position>
      <detail>NSW-Chippendale, Named most promising company, also named best place to work and at the cutting edge of media advertising to all mediums. Due to ongoing internal improvements, we are now on the hunt for a Senior Software Development Engineer who has a proven track record in development with a strong integration focus. As a Senior Front End Development Engineer, your core responsibilities will include, but would de</detail>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/Senior-Front-End-Developer-Job-Chippendale-NSW-AU-167232445.aspx</link>
      <guid>167232445</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:41:13 GMT</pubDate>
   </jobAlert>
   <jobAlert>
      <position>.NET Developer</position>
      <detail>SA-Adelaide, Significant ICT Project Great Rate Adelaide CBD Location Hudson is a preferred ICT Contract and Permanent staffing supplier to the Defence, Federal / State Government, Education, Financial institutions and many major commercial ASX listed and small to medium companies. With multiple opportunities available within high profile projects across South Australia, we have some exciting contract roles av</detail>
      <link>http://jobview.careerone.com.au/NET-Developer-Job-Adelaide-SA-AU-167428993.aspx</link>
      <guid>167428993</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 20:39:59 GMT</pubDate>
   </jobAlert>
</jobAlerts>
